[{"answer": "Dr. Murray's repeated incompetent and unskilled acts that led to Mr. Jackson's death.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Who caused the death of Michael Jackson?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, absolutely.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Because you can argue it's either way, can't you, on this?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's tough to say.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Who had the better day, do you think?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Yes, the defense is a little bit multilayered in that they're saying that Jackson had a horrible insomnia problem and he used Propofol to get over it and Murray when he came on board understood this and used this as well with the anticipation of weaning him off of it.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Is that really the crux of this court case?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "I saw that this morning, and when I heard the tape, I could not believe what I was hearing.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "What was your reaction to those two things?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yes, I mean, what does it show you, though, given that it was taken -- the recording was made in May before he died, two months or so before he died.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "I mean, if that doesn't show you, don't you think that was enough?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "That's what I was wondering, A, why, Michael would never let anyone tape him.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "What does that tell you?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "I thought it was very suspicious.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Did you find it suspicious?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "I saw him standing outside of the room where Mrs. Jackson and the family and the cousins were, and the children, just crying and not understanding what was going on.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Did you see Conrad Murray at all that day?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "To tell you the truth, I think that they have all been in such pain.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "What do you think the family believe really happened?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "No, listen, Kathy, I know this is a very difficult thing to discuss and I do appreciate you coming on today.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "And I believe that he really trusted that this doctor would be there to be helpful and on call and -- I say that again?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "You know, it's interesting, Piers, because the law's a little bit vague on this.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "I'm curious, is it actually lawful for any doctor to administer Propofol in a private home in this manner?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "No, I think it's suspicious.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "From a medical standpoint, as a doctor, do you find that suspicious or do you think that someone who has just seen Michael Jackson die in his care has just freaked out a bit and maybe just wasn't thinking straight?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, you know, at first -- I mean I'll preface by saying the whole thing is so bizarre.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Does any of that sound credible to you?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, I think that it's going to be very important that the audience knows, Piers, that seven of these jurors actually have drug or alcohol abuse in their immediate families.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "What was your initial assessment of the behavioral pattern today?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "It's a tremendously important component for the prosecutors because prosecutors around the country are always worried that they have to step up to the plate and create situations such as \"CSI\" does.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "How much does that come into play in a case like this, do you think?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "David did an excellent job in his opening statement.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "How did he do today, do you think, in laying out his case?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "You know, I had the same feeling as the counsel that just spoke earlier.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "What was your feeling as the day unraveled?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "I absolutely think that he made up ground today.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Is that going to be a major problem for him?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I think it's very significant.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "How significant is this debate over his health before he died, do you think, going to be?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "It's not.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Is that a credible position for them to take, do you think?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I don't think it's fair.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Is it fair to just label him as somebody who has been negligent and simply just allowed Michael Jackson to take far too many drugs and die?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Gentlemen, thank you all very much.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Is there a reasonable doubt as to that or not?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "It's important to me because I think there's an injustice being done.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Why is it so important to you?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "They didn't sequester the jury.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "What kind of things?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "So you watched him save your life, effectively?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "The misunderstanding about Conrad is his compassion and his love for people.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "For people who don't know Conrad Murray, what is the misunderstanding about the kind of man he is?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I was at home.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "And particularly, what were you thinking when you heard that Conrad was there at the time and had been the doctor that night in the house?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "He's the most compassionate man that I've ever met.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "What's your view?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Do you think he saved your life?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I spoke with him before he went to work with Michael.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "How did Conrad find himself in this position?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Is that a picture you could recognize?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Let me share something with you and I'd like to elaborate on that a little bit.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Is it possible that he was negligent, do you think?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Your honor, I'm an innocent man.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "How do you plead?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Basically, Piers, the reason I'm here is to let people know he is not the animal that they are portraying him to be.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "As somebody that knows the man well and believes he saved your life, how do you feel about the way his reputation has been put through the mincer like this?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "That's ridiculous.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "So when people say that he is greedy and was only working for Michael Jackson for money and fame and so on, what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Money was not his motivating factor?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "That's why he was broke.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "He has never -- or in the last five years, charged me for any office calls, any examinations, nothing, you know?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Is Conrad Murray the kind of man that in that situation, when he probably needed the money, and probably enjoyed the attachment to Michael Jackson -- could you have imagined him bowing to that kind of pressure?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Certainly.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Ruby, if required, will you give evidence on his behalf in court?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "OK, in my case, let me tell you, I was having problems with my heart and didn't even know it.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "In your case, Ruby, what did he do for you?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "No, his quick thinking and proactiveness.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "In your view, his quick thinking saved your life?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Anything's possible, but I doubt it very seriously.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "Could he have had his judgment impaired, do you think, by that dynamic?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Piers, if I knew all of the -- all of the fundamentals of this case, I might be able to answer that.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "What do you think is the right verdict here?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Absolutely no doubt.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Your belief, like all of you, is that there's no way he would have done anything to have deliberately imperiled Michael Jackson's life?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Not somebody who works the way that he works with people, and comes to your house to make sure you are all right, and works for free.", "docId": "110927pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "None of you believe that is possible, knowing Conrad Murray?", "qSentId": 570}]